<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Testimonials on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/testimonials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Testimonials on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 08:23:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/testimonials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ross Cormack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/testimonials/rosscormack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 08:23:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/testimonials/rosscormack/</guid>
      <description>Project: Chevron Rosebank FEED (FPSO and subsea tie-back deep-water development, West of Shetland, UK)
 “It was a pleasure working with Lynne on the Chevron Rosebank Project. Lynne combines a well structured approach to work with an organised mind and highly creative problem solving skills which were well suited to a fast paced FEED project. Lynne is approachable and friendly, knowledgeable of safety and environmental regulations and best practices in industry, diligent and determined when it comes to preparing deliverables, giving presentations or sharing information, and generally brightens the office environment and is a pleasure to work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Brock</title>
      <link>http://example.org/testimonials/chrisbrock/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 08:23:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/testimonials/chrisbrock/</guid>
      <description>Project: Premier Oates Drilling Program
“ Lynne works well within teams and with clients. We have used her and her team a number of times for environmental auditing and surveying and her findings have helped improve our own environmental performance in drilling.‬ ”‬‬‬
‪CHRIS BROCK‬‬
WELLS ENGINEERING EHS ADVISOR AT TULLOW OIL‬ (FORMERLY PREMIER OIL HSE ADVISOR)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bojan Paunavic</title>
      <link>http://example.org/testimonials/bojanpaunavic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 15:54:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/testimonials/bojanpaunavic/</guid>
      <description>‪Project: Chevron Rosebank FEED (FPSO and subsea tie-back deep-water development, West of Shetland, UK)
“ I had the pleasure of working with Lynne Ramsey on the Chevron Rosebank Project from 2012 until 2014. During this period Lynne was responsible for, amongst other duties, collating the technical data for the Project Environmental Statement. This required extensive input from various company groups in order to satisfy UK legislation, international regulations and industry standards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>